<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Uncertain Ecologist</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Uncertain Ecologist</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic Shinydashboard CV</title>
      <link>/post/academic_r_shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/academic_r_shiny/</guid>
      <description>Building an Academic CV ShinyDashboardInspired by Prof. Mark Reed’s infographic CV (see: https://www.fasttrackimpact.com/post/2019/06/06/how-to-make-an-infographic-cv-featuring-impact-that-you-could-actually-submit-with-your-n) I decided to see if I could make a ShinyDashboard version. My first attempt can be found at: https://drmatt.shinyapps.io/AcademicCVShinyDashboard/
It still needs a lot of work to make it more visually appealling, but I think its a good starting point.
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning R resources</title>
      <link>/post/learning-r-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/learning-r-resources/</guid>
      <description>Learning R: where to startSwirl (https://swirlstats.com/)I really like the swirl package in R that has several modules available for learning and understanding how R works. It leads you by the hand through straight forward courses that are carried out through the R console. There are a number of additional courses available (see: https://github.com/swirldev/swirl_courses#swirl-courses). Adventr is another package that does a similar thing - interactive tutorials, but I have not used that one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopping for species</title>
      <link>/post/shopping-for-species/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/shopping-for-species/</guid>
      <description>Can we use association rules to identify co-occurring species?Machine learning has been occupying my thoughts recently as I am reading the book Machine Learning with R by Brett Lantz (https://www.amazon.com/dp/1782162143?tag=inspiredalgor-20). I am interested in making the algorithms described in the book useful for my work in applied conservation science.
Unsurprisingly a lot of effort in machine-learning has been focused on increasing sales. One area where this has shown rapid growth is in grocery shops where loyalty cards have allowed data to be collected on our transactions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>